Wilcox College of Nursing Records
© 2005 University of Connecticut
- Series II: Personnel, Students & Curriculum, undated, 1907-1997
  - Curriculum
    - Listing of courses and professors, 1908-1909 (Box 21:, Folder 179)
    - Advanced Composition: syllabus, 1991 Spring (Box 21:, Folder 180)
    - Anatomy and Physiology
      - Exams, syllabus, 1989-1990 (Box 21:, Folder 181)
      - Exams, 1990-1991 (Box 21:, Folder 182)
      - Course outline, Bibliography, 1991 Fall (Box 21:, Folder 183)
    - Anatomy and Physiology II
      - Exams, 1989-1990 (Box 21:, Folder 184)
      - Exams, syllabus, 1990-1991 (Box 21:, Folder 185)
      - Course outline, bibliography, 1992 Spring (Box 21:, Folder 186)
    - Assessment of the Patient's Level of Adaptation
      - Syllabus, 1989 (Box 21:, Folder 187)
      - Syllabus, assessment tool, 1990 (Box 21:, Folder 188)
    - Biochemistry: Exam, 1989-1990 (Box 21:, Folder 189)
    - Body Rhythmics, 1948 (Box 21:, Folder 190)
    - Chemistry
      - Exams, Syllabus, 1989-1990 (Box 21:, Folder 191)
      - Exams, Syllabus, 1990-1991 (Box 21:, Folder 192)
    - Concepts for the Practice of Nursing
      - Syllabus, Bibliography, 1992 (Box 21:, Folder 193)
      - Course Outline, 1993 Spring (Box 21:, Folder 194)
      - Syllabus, course requirements, Bibliography, guidelines, 1995-1996 (Box 21:, Folder 195)
    - Concepts of Professional Nursing: Exams, 1989-1990 (Box 22:, Folder 196)
    - Developmental Psychology II: syllabus, 1991, 1993 (Box 22:, Folder 197)
    - Elementary Statistics: syllabus, 1992 Spring (Box 22:, Folder 198)
    - English 101: syllabus, 1989, 1994 (Box 22:, Folder 199)
    - Fundamentals of Nursing
      - Exams, syllabus, assessment tool, 1989-1990 (Box 22:, Folder 200)
      - Exams, assessment tool and Bibliography, 1990-1991 (Box 22:, Folder 201)
      - Course outline and exams, 1994-1995 (Box 22:, Folder 202)
    - Introduction to Nutrition: syllabus, 1989 Fall (Box 22:, Folder 203)
    - Introduction to Sociology: Syllabus, course outlines, 1989, 1991, 1994 (Box 22:, Folder 204)
    - Mental Health Nursing
      - Syllabus, bibliography, assessment, 1990 (Box 22:, Folder 205)
      - Syllabus, tool for assessment, 1992 (Box 22:, Folder 206)
    - Microbiology
      - Exams, 1989-1990 (Box 22:, Folder 207)
      - Exam, Syllabus, 1990-1991 (Box 22:, Folder 208)
      - Course Outline, Bibliography, 1992 Spring (Box 22:, Folder 209)
    - Nursing Across the Lifespan
      - Exam, Syllabus, assessment, 1990-1991 (Box 22:, Folder 210)
      - Course Outline, assessment, 1992-1993 (Box 22:, Folder 211)
      - Syllabus, biblio, assessment, 1993 (Box 22:, Folder 212)
      - Syllabus, exam, assessment, 1994-1995 (Box 23:, Folder 213)
    - Nursing of the Adult I
      - Syllabus, bibliography, assessment, 1989 (Box 23:, Folder 214)
      - Course outline, assessment tool, 1992-1993 (Box 23:, Folder 215)
      - Syllabus, exams, quizzes, hand-outs, 1996 (Box 23:, Folder 216)
    - Nursing of the Adult II
      - Exams, 1988-1989 (Box 23:, Folder 217)
      - Evaluations, hand-outs, 1988 (Box 23:, Folder 218)
      - Syllabus, course requirements, 1989 (Box 23:, Folder 219)
      - Syllabus, bibliography, 1991 Fall (Box 23:, Folder 220)
      - Course outline, assessment tool, 1992 (Box 23:, Folder 221)
      - Course syllabus, assessment tool, 1995 (Box 23:, Folder 222)
      - Exams, syllabus, 1990-1991 (Box 23:, Folder 223)
    - Nursing of the Adult III
      - Syllabus, 1991-1992 (Box 23:, Folder 224)
      - Syllabus, 1992 (Box 23:, Folder 225)
      - Course outline, assessment tool, 1993-1994 (Box 24:, Folder 226)
      - Syllabus, exams, bibliography, 1995-1996 (Box 24:, Folder 227)
    - Nursing of the Adult with Complex Health Needs
      - Syllabus, bibliography, assessment tool, 1989 (Box 24:, Folder 228)
      - Syllabus, bibliography, 1991-1992 (Box 24:, Folder 229)
    - Nursing of the Childbearing Family
      - Syllabus, 1990 (Box 24:, Folder 230)
      - Syllabus, 1991 (Box 24:, Folder 231)
    - Nursing of Children
      - Syllabus, bibliography, 1990 (Box 24:, Folder 232)
      - Syllabus, 1991 (Box 24:, Folder 233)
    - Nursing Leadership
      - Syllabus, bibliography, 1989-1990 (Box 24:, Folder 234)
      - Exams, syllabus, bibliography, assessment, 1990-1991 (Box 24:, Folder 235)
      - Syllabus, bibliography, assessment, 1991-1992 (Box 24:, Folder 236)
    - Organic Chemistry: Exams, 1989-1991 (Box 24:, Folder 237)
    - Professional Adjustment I: syllabus, 1965-1966 (Box 24:, Folder 238)
    - Psychology 101: syllabus, course outline, 1990-1993 (Box 24:, Folder 239)
    - Psychology 204: syllabus, 1989 Fall (Box 24:, Folder 240)
    - The Test Manual, circa 1990 (Box 25:, Folder 241)
    - Curriculum Plans- Day Division, 1983-1997 (Box 25:, Folder 242)
    - Curriculum Plans- Evening Division, 1983-1997 (Box 25:, Folder 243)
    - Nursing Services Rendered by Student Nurses, 1963-1964 (Box 25:, Folder 244)
    - Nursing Services Rendered by Student Nurses, 1964-1965 (Box 25:, Folder 245)
    - Nursing Services Rendered by Student Nurses, 1965-1966 (Box 25:, Folder 246)
    - Nursing Services Rendered by Student Nurses, 1966-1967 (Box 25:, Folder 247)
    - Nursing Services Rendered by Student Nurses, 1967-1968 (Box 25:, Folder 248)
    - Nursing Services Rendered by Student Nurses, 1968-1969 (Box 25:, Folder 249)
  - Affiliations
    - Forham Hospital, 1967-1971 (Box 26:, Folder 250)
    - Middlesex Community College
      - Correspondence, 1967-1969 (Box 26:, Folder 251)
      - Correspondence, 1970-1974 (Box 26:, Folder 252)
      - Plans and correspondence, meeting minutes, 1983-1994 (Box 26:, Folder 253)
    - University of Hartford plan
      - Correspondence and reports, 1984-1985 (Box 26:, Folder 254)
      - Correspondence and notes, 1986 (Box 26:, Folder 255)
      - Correspondence and notes, 1987 (Box 26:, Folder 256)
      - Correspondence and notes, 1988 (Box 26:, Folder 257)
      - Reports, 1985-1988 (Box 26:, Folder 258)
      - Press release & advertisements, undated (Box 26:, Folder 259)
      - Initial proposal for Co-op program, 1985 Sept (Box 26:, Folder 260)
      - Revised proposal, 1985 September (Box 26:, Folder 261)
      - Model for BSN degree to State, 1985 October 31 (Box 26:, Folder 262)
      - Model for BSN degree to NLN, 1985 December (Box 26:, Folder 263)
    - Three Rivers Community Technical College- course model, 1992-1993 (Box 27:, Folder 264)
    - CT Articulation Model, 1991 (Box 27:, Folder 265)
      - Response to validation criteria, 1991 (Box 27:, Folder 266)
    - CT Articulation Model, 1992 (Box 27:, Folder 267)
      - Notes, minutes, correspondence, 1992 (Box 27:, Folder 268)
      - Minutes, correspondence, 1995-1996 (Box 27:, Folder 269)
- Series III: Administration, undated, 1909-1997
  - Committee Meeting Minutes
    - Advisory Council on Nursing Education, 1948-1949 (Box 28:, Folder 270)
    - Advisory Council on Nursing Education, 1962 (Box 28:, Folder 271)
    - Advisory Council on Nursing Education, 1968-1969 (Box 28:, Folder 272)
    - Advisory Council on Nursing Education, 1969-1970 (Box 28:, Folder 273)
    - Long-range Planning sub-committee on Ed. & Research, 1968-1969 (Box 28:, Folder 274)
    - Long-range Planning sub-committee on Ed. & Research, 1969-1970 (Box 28:, Folder 275)
    - Alumni Association (laws & articles), circa 1974 (Box 28:, Folder 276)
    - Student Personnel Services Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 28:, Folder 277)
    - Student Personnel Services Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 28:, Folder 278)
    - Faculty Organization, 1978-1979 (Box 28:, Folder 279)
    - Other Committee Minutes, 1978-1979 (Box 28:, Folder 280)
    - Student Personnel Services Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 28:, Folder 281)
    - Other Committee Minutes, 1979-1980 (Box 28:, Folder 282)
    - Student Personnel Services Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 28:, Folder 283)
    - Committee Annual Reports, 1980-1981 (Box 28:, Folder 284)
    - Admissions Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 28:, Folder 285)
    - Clinical Instructor Meetings, 1981 (Box 28:, Folder 286)
    - Curriculum Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 28:, Folder 287)
    - Faculty Bill of Rights and Responsibilities, 1980-1981 (Box 28:, Folder 288)
    - Faculty Development Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 28:, Folder 289)
    - Faculty Organization, 1980 September - December (Box 28:, Folder 290)
    - Faculty Organization, 1981 January - April (Box 28:, Folder 291)
    - Faculty Organization, 1981 May - August (Box 28:, Folder 292)
    - Library Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 28:, Folder 293)
    - Management Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 29:, Folder 294)
    - Other Meeting Minutes, 1980-1981 (Box 29:, Folder 295)
    - Scholarship and Awards Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 29:, Folder 296)
    - Student Personnel Services Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 29:, Folder 297)
    - Committee Annual Reports, 1981-1982 (Box 29:, Folder 298)
    - Admissions Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 29:, Folder 299)
    - Admissions Committee, 1982 March - June (Box 29:, Folder 300)
    - Curriculum Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 29:, Folder 301)
    - Faculty Development Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 29:, Folder 302)
    - Faculty Organization, 1981-1982 (Box 29:, Folder 303)
    - Library Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 29:, Folder 304)
    - Management Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 29:, Folder 305)
    - Other Meeting Minutes, 1981-1982 (Box 29:, Folder 306)
    - Scholarship and Awards Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 29:, Folder 307)
    - Student Personnel Services Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 29:, Folder 308)
    - AD-HOC Faculty Evaluation Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 29:, Folder 309)
    - AD-HOC Committee of Admissions on L.P.N. Challenge, 1982-1983 (Box 29:, Folder 310)
    - Admissions Committee, 1982-1983 March (Box 30:, Folder 311)
    - Admissions Committee, 1983 April - August (Box 30:, Folder 312)
    - Curriculum Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 30:, Folder 313)
    - Faculty Development Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 30:, Folder 314)
    - Faculty Organization, 1982-1983Jan (Box 30:, Folder 315)
    - Faculty Organization, 1983 January - June (Box 30:, Folder 316)
    - Library Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 30:, Folder 317)
    - Management Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 31:, Folder 318)
    - Other Committee Minutes, 1982-1983 (Box 31:, Folder 319)
    - Scholarship and Awards Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 31:, Folder 320)
    - Student Personnel Services Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 31:, Folder 321)
    - Management Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 31:, Folder 322)
    - Management Committee, 1984-1985 (Box 31:, Folder 323)
    - Other Meeting Minutes, 1984-1985 (Box 31:, Folder 324)
    - Management Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 31:, Folder 325)
    - Other Committee Minutes, 1985-1986 (Box 31:, Folder 326)
    - Management Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 32:, Folder 327)
    - Annual Committee Reports, 1987-1988 (Box 32:, Folder 328)
    - Nursing Education Task Force Committee, 1987 December 4 (Box 32:, Folder 329)
    - Nursing Education Task Force Committee, 1988 February 18 (Box 32:, Folder 330)
      - Minutes and notes, 1988 March 18 (Box 32:, Folder 331)
    - Nursing Education Task Force Committee, 1988 May 24 (Box 32:, Folder 332)
    - Nursing Education Task Force Committee, 1988 July 26 (Box 32:, Folder 333)
    - Management Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 32:, Folder 334)
    - Other Meeting Minutes, 1987-1988 (Box 32:, Folder 335)
    - Annual Committee Reports, 1988-1989 (Box 32:, Folder 336)
    - Curriculum Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 32:, Folder 337)
    - Faculty Organization, 1988-1989 (Box 32:, Folder 338)
    - Other Meeting Minutes, 1988-1989 (Box 32:, Folder 339)
    - Planning Committee Minutes, 1988-1989 (Box 32:, Folder 340)
    - Student Personnel Services Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 32:, Folder 341)
    - Annual Committee Reports, 1989-1990 (Box 32:, Folder 342)
    - AD-HOC NCLEX Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 32:, Folder 343)
    - Curriculum Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 32:, Folder 344)
    - Faculty Development Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 32:, Folder 345)
    - Faculty Organization, 1989 August - December (Box 32:, Folder 346)
    - Faculty Organization, 1990 January - June (Box 32:, Folder 347)
    - Library Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 32:, Folder 348)
    - Other Committee Minutes, 1989-1990 (Box 32:, Folder 349)
    - Recruitment and Admissions Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 32:, Folder 350)
    - Scholarship Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 32:, Folder 351)
    - Student Personnel Services Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 32:, Folder 352)
    - Committee Annual Reports, 1990-1991 (Box 34:, Folder 353)
    - Curriculum Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 34:, Folder 354)
    - Faculty Development Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 34:, Folder 355)
    - Faculty Organization, 1990 August (Box 34:, Folder 356)
    - Faculty Organization, 1990-1991 February (Box 34:, Folder 357)
    - Faculty Organization, 1991 March - June (Box 34:, Folder 358)
    - Library Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 34:, Folder 359)
    - Other Committee Minutes, 1990-1991 (Box 34:, Folder 360)
    - Recruitment and Admissions Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 34:, Folder 361)
    - Scholarship and Awards Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 34:, Folder 362)
    - Student Personnel Services Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 34:, Folder 363)
    - Testing Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 34:, Folder 364)
    - Annual Committee Reports, 1991-1992 (Box 35:, Folder 365)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 35:, Folder 366)
    - Board of Director's Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 35:, Folder 367)
    - Curriculum Committee, 1991 October 30 (Box 35:, Folder 368)
    - Curriculum Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 35:, Folder 369)
    - Curriculum Committee: Recommendations for next year, 1991-1992 (Box 35:, Folder 370)
    - Faculty Affairs Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 35:, Folder 371)
    - Faculty Senate, 1991-1992 February (Box 35:, Folder 372)
    - Faculty Senate, 1992 March - June (Box 35:, Folder 373)
    - Other Committee Minutes, 1991-1992 (Box 36:, Folder 374)
    - Recruitment, Admissions, Progression & Grad. Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 36:, Folder 375)
    - Steering Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 36:, Folder 376)
    - Student Affairs Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 36:, Folder 377)
    - Testing Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 36:, Folder 378)
    - Annual Committee Reports, 1992-1993 (Box 36:, Folder 379)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 36:, Folder 380)
    - Board of Director's Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 36:, Folder 381)
    - Curriculum Committee, 1992-1993 February (Box 36:, Folder 382)
    - Curriculum Committee, 1993 March - May (Box 36:, Folder 383)
    - Executive Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 36:, Folder 384)
    - Faculty Affairs Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 36:, Folder 385)
    - Annual Committee Reports, 1992-1993 (Box 37:, Folder 386)
    - Faculty Senate, 1992 August - December (Box 37:, Folder 387)
    - Faculty Senate, 1993 January - June (Box 37:, Folder 388)
    - Other Meeting Minutes, 1992-1993 (Box 37:, Folder 389)
    - Recruitment and Admissions Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 37:, Folder 390)
    - Special Curriculum Committee, 1992-1993 March (Box 37:, Folder 391)
    - Special Curriculum Committee, 1993 April - June (Box 37:, Folder 392)
    - Student Affairs Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 37:, Folder 393)
    - Testing Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 37:, Folder 394)
    - Annual Committee Reports, 1993-1994 (Box 38:, Folder 395)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 38:, Folder 396)
    - Board of Director's Committee, 1993 September 2 (Box 38:, Folder 397)
    - Board of Director's Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 38:, Folder 398)
    - Board of Director's Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 38:, Folder 399)
    - Board of Director's Committee, 1994 July 24 (Box 38:, Folder 400)
    - College Senate Committee, 1993 August - December (Box 38:, Folder 401)
    - College Senate Committee, 1994 January - June (Box 38:, Folder 402)
    - Curriculum Committee, 1993 September - December (Box 38:, Folder 403)
    - Curriculum Committee, 1994 January - June (Box 39:, Folder 404)
    - Executive Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 39:, Folder 405)
    - Faculty Affairs Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 39:, Folder 406)
    - Other Meeting Minutes, 1993-1994 (Box 39:, Folder 407)
    - Professional Staff Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 39:, Folder 408)
    - Recruitment and Admissions Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 39:, Folder 409)
    - Student Affairs Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 39:, Folder 410)
    - AD-HOC Bylaws of Wilcox, circa 1994 (Box 39:, Folder 411)
    - Annual Committee Reports, 1994-1995 (Box 40:, Folder 412)
    - Board of Director's Committee, 1994-1995 (Box 40:, Folder 413)
    - College Senate Committee, 1994-1995 (Box 40:, Folder 414)
    - Curriculum Committee, 1994-1995 (Box 40:, Folder 415)
    - Executive Committee, 1994-1995 (Box 40:, Folder 416)
    - Faculty Affairs Committee, 1994-1995 (Box 40:, Folder 417)
    - Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1994-1995 (Box 40:, Folder 418)
    - Other Meeting Minutes, 1994-1995 (Box 40:, Folder 419)
    - Professional Staff Committee, 1994-1995 (Box 40:, Folder 420)
    - Recruitment and Admissions Committee, 1994-1995 (Box 40:, Folder 421)
    - Students Affairs Committee, 1994-1995 (Box 40:, Folder 422)
    - Annual Committee Reports, 1995-1996 (Box 40:, Folder 423)
    - Faculty Affairs Committee, 1995-1996 (Box 41:, Folder 424)
    - Board of Director's Report: Closure, 1995 August (Box 41:, Folder 425)
    - Board of Director's Committee, 1995-1996 (Box 41:, Folder 426)
    - College Senate Minutes, 1995-1996 (Box 41:, Folder 427)
    - Curriculum Committee, 1995-1996 (Box 41:, Folder 428)
    - Executive Committee, 1995-1996 (Box 41:, Folder 429)
    - Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1995-1996 (Box 41:, Folder 430)
    - Other Meeting Minutes, 1995-1996 (Box 41:, Folder 431)
    - Other meeting Minutes & Notes on Closure/ transformation, 1995-1996 (Box 41:, Folder 432)
    - Student Affairs Committee, 1995-1996 (Box 41:, Folder 433)
    - Board of Director's Meeting Minutes, 1996-1997 (Box 41:, Folder 434)
    - Board of Director's Meeting Re: Closure, 1997 December (Box 41:, Folder 435)
    - Campus Community Team Minutes, 1996-1997 (Box 41:, Folder 436)
    - Meeting Minutes, 1996-1997 (Box 41:, Folder 437)
    - Meeting Minutes, 1997-1998 (Box 41:, Folder 438)
    - Nursing Committee Minutes, 1930-1935 (Box 42:, Folder 439)
    - Nursing Committee Minutes, 1936-1941 (Box 42:, Folder 440)
    - Nursing Committee Minutes, 1941-1946 (Box 42:, Folder 441)
    - Nursing Committee Minutes, 1946-1951 (Box 42:, Folder 442)
    - Nursing Committee Minutes, 1951-1955 (Box 42:, Folder 443)
    - Nursing Committee Minutes, 1955-1960 (Box 42:, Folder 444)
    - Nursing Committee Minutes, 1960-1965 (Box 42:, Folder 445)
    - Nursing Committee Minutes, 1965-1970 (Box 42:, Folder 446)
    - ADN Planning Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 43:, Folder 447)
      - Criteria (booklets), 1987-1990 (Box 43:, Folder 448)
      - Curriculum revision proposal, undated (Box 43:, Folder 449)
      - Faculty requirements and policies, circa 1990 (Box 43:, Folder 450)
      - Reports related to Accreditation, 1991-1993 (Box 43:, Folder 451)
      - Accreditation correspondence, 1989-1993 (Box 43:, Folder 452)
      - NEAS&C, 1989-1993 (Box 43:, Folder 453)
      - Finances, undated (Box 43:, Folder 454)
  - Reports
    - Annual Report, 1909 November 1 (Box 44:, Folder 455)
    - Quarter Report, 1910 (Box 44:, Folder 456)
    - Quarter Reports, 1911 (Box 44:, Folder 457)
    - Quarter Reports, 1912 (Box 44:, Folder 458)
    - Quarter Reports, 1914 (Box 44:, Folder 459)
    - Quarter Reports, 1915 (Box 44:, Folder 460)
    - Monthly / Quarterly Reports, 1916 (Box 44:, Folder 461)
    - Quarter Reports, 1917 (Box 44:, Folder 462)
    - Monthly / Yearly Reports, 1918 (Box 44:, Folder 463)
    - Monthly Reports, 1919 (Box 44:, Folder 464)
    - Monthly Reports, 1920 (Box 44:, Folder 465)
    - Yearly Report and Monthly Reports, 1921 (Box 44:, Folder 466)
    - Monthly Reports, 1922 (Box 44:, Folder 467)
    - Monthly Reports, 1923 (Box 44:, Folder 468)
    - Monthly Reports, 1924 (Box 44:, Folder 469)
    - Monthly Reports, 1925 (Box 44:, Folder 470)
    - Monthly Reports, 1926 (Box 44:, Folder 471)
    - Monthly Reports, 1927 (Box 44:, Folder 472)
    - Monthly Reports, 1928 (Box 44:, Folder 473)
    - Monthly Reports, 1929 (Box 44:, Folder 474)
    - Monthly Reports, 1930 (Box 44:, Folder 475)
    - Monthly Reports, 1931 (Box 44:, Folder 476)
    - Monthly Reports, 1932 (Box 44:, Folder 477)
    - Educational Report, 1946-1947 (Box 44:, Folder 478)
    - Educational Report, 1947-1948 (Box 44:, Folder 479)
    - Monthly Reports, 1947-1948 (Box 44:, Folder 480)
    - Educational Report, 1948-1949 (Box 44:, Folder 481)
    - Monthly Reports, 1948-1949 (Box 44:, Folder 482)
    - Educational Report, 1949-1950 (Box 44:, Folder 483)
    - Monthly Reports, 1949-1950 (Box 44:, Folder 484)
    - Educational Report, 1950-1951 (Box 44:, Folder 485)
    - Monthly Reports, 1950-1951 (Box 44:, Folder 486)
    - Educational Report, 1951-1952 (Box 44:, Folder 487)
    - Monthly Reports, 1951-1952 (Box 44:, Folder 488)
    - Educational Report, 1952-1953 (Box 45:, Folder 489)
    - Monthly Reports, 1952-1953 (Box 45:, Folder 490)
    - Educational Report, 1953-1954 (Box 45:, Folder 491)
    - Monthly Reports, 1953-1954 (Box 45:, Folder 492)
    - Educational Report, 1954-1955 (Box 45:, Folder 493)
    - Educational Report, 1955-1956 (Box 45:, Folder 494)
    - Educational Report, 1956-1957 (Box 45:, Folder 495)
    - Monthly Reports, 1956-1957 (Box 45:, Folder 496)
    - Educational Report, 1957-1958 (Box 45:, Folder 497)
    - Monthly Reports, 1957-1958 (Box 45:, Folder 498)
    - Educational Report, 1958-1959 (Box 45:, Folder 499)
    - Monthly Reports, 1958-1959 (Box 45:, Folder 500)
    - Educational Report, 1959-1960 (Box 45:, Folder 501)
    - Monthly Reports, 1959-1960 (Box 45:, Folder 502)
    - Educational Report, 1960-1961 (Box 45:, Folder 503)
    - Monthly Reports, 1960-1961 (Box 45:, Folder 504)
    - Educational Report, 1961-1962 (Box 45:, Folder 505)
    - Monthly Reports, 1961-1962 (Box 45:, Folder 506)
    - Educational Report, 1962-1963 (Box 45:, Folder 507)
    - Monthly Reports, 1962-1963 (Box 45:, Folder 508)
    - Educational Report, 1963-1964 (Box 45:, Folder 509)
    - Monthly Reports, 1963-1964 (Box 45:, Folder 510)
    - Annual and Educational Report, 1964-1965 (Box 45:, Folder 511)
    - Monthly Reports, 1964-1965 (Box 45:, Folder 512)
    - Annual and Educational Report, 1965-1966 (Box 46:, Folder 513)
    - Monthly Reports, 1965-1966 (Box 46:, Folder 514)
    - Annual and Educational Report, 1966-1967 (Box 46:, Folder 515)
    - Monthly Reports, 1966-1967 (Box 46:, Folder 516)
    - Annual and Educational Report, 1967-1968 (Box 46:, Folder 517)
    - Monthly Reports, 1967-1968 (Box 46:, Folder 518)
    - Annual and Educational Report, 1968-1969 (Box 46:, Folder 519)
    - Monthly Reports, 1968-1969 (Box 46:, Folder 520)
    - Annual Report, 1969-1970 (Box 46:, Folder 521)
    - Monthly Reports, 1969-1970 (Box 46:, Folder 522)
    - Annual Report, 1970-1971 (Box 46:, Folder 523)
    - Monthly Reports, 1970-1971 (Box 46:, Folder 524)
    - Annual Report, 1971-1972 (Box 46:, Folder 525)
    - Monthly Reports, 1971-1972 (Box 46:, Folder 526)
    - Annual Report, 1972-1973 (Box 46:, Folder 527)
    - Monthly Reports, 1972-1973 (Box 46:, Folder 528)
    - Annual Report, 1973-1974 (Box 46:, Folder 529)
    - Monthly Reports, 1973-1974 (Box 46:, Folder 530)
    - Annual Report, 1974-1975 (Box 46:, Folder 531)
    - Monthly Reports, 1974-1975 (Box 46:, Folder 532)
    - Annual Report, 1975-1976 (Box 46:, Folder 533)
    - Monthly Reports, 1975-1976 (Box 46:, Folder 534)
    - Annual Report, 1976-1977 (Box 46:, Folder 535)
    - Monthly Reports, 1976-1977 (Box 46:, Folder 536)
    - Annual Report, 1977-1978 (Box 46:, Folder 537)
    - Monthly Reports, 1977-1978 (Box 46:, Folder 538)